

C129, The 3rd Engineering Building, Yonsei University, 120-749, Seoul, Rep. of KOREA

□ (+82) 10-9426-4154 | ☑ read12300@yonsei.ac.kr | 🏕 diml.yonsei.ac.kr | 🛅 read12300 | 😘 read12300@naver.com

"Time is gold, friends"

Summary_

I am currently a Ph.D. student with School of Electrical and Electronic Engineering at Yonsei University, directed by Prof. Kwanghoon Sohn. Before that, I obtained my bachelor degree from the Yonsei University. My research interests include variational method and continous optimization, both in theory and applications in image processing, machine learning, and computer vision.

Education

Yonsei University Seoul, S.Korea

Ph.D. Candidate in Electrical and Electronic Engineering

- Mar. 2013 Present · Major: Image Processing and Computer Vision
- Supervisor: Prof. Kwanghoon Sohn
- Overall GPA: 4.0/4.3

Yonsei University Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONIC ENGINEERING Mar. 2007 - Exp. Feb. 2013

- Major: Electrical and Electronic Engineering
- Overall GPA: **3.64**/4.3

Experience

University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign

Seoul, S.Korea

VISITING SCHOLAR AT COORDINATED SCIENCE LAB

Nov. 2017 - Feb. 2018

· Research with Prof. Minh N. Do

Yonsei University Seoul, S.Korea

RESEARCH ASSISTANT AT DIGITAL IMAGE MEDIA LAB

Mar. 2013 - Present

- Research with Prof. Kwanghoon Sohn
- Participation in several research projects

Research Interest_

Image Processing

- Variational method and continous optimization
- Edge-aware filtering, denoising, deblurring, super-resolution, etc.

Computer Vision

- · Stereo matching, optical flow, depth refinement, etc.
- Deep learning for image resotration, segmentation, and representation

Publications

International Journal

- Y. Kim, "Structure-texture image decomposition using deep variational priors," In Preparing.
- Y. Kim, H. Jung, D. Min, and K. Sohn, "A deep variational approach for single image depth estimation," IEEE Trans. on Image Processing (TIP), (Major Revision).
- Y. Kim, D. Min, B. Ham, and K. Sohn, "Fast domain decomposition for global image smoothing," IEEE Trans. on Image Processing (TIP), vol. 26, no. 8, pp. 4079-91, Aug, 2017.
- Y. Kim, B. Ham, C. Oh, and K. Sohn, "Structure selective depth super-resolution for RGB-D cameras," IEEE Trans. on Image Processing (TIP), vol. 25, no. 11, pp. 5227-38, Nov, 2016.
- S. Choi, D. Min, B. Ham, Y. Kim, C. Oh, and K. Sohn, "Depth Analogy: data-driven approach for single image depth estimation using gradient samples," IEEE Trans. on Image Processing (TIP), vol. 24, no. 12, pp. 5953-66, Dec, 2015.

International Conference

- J. Cho, Y. Kim, C. Oh, and K. Sohn, "Multi-task self-supervised visual representation learning for monocular road segmentation," IEEE Conf. on Multimedia and Expo (ICME), (Submitted).
- Y. Kim, H. Jung, D. Min, and K. Sohn, "Deeply aggregated alternating minimization for image restoration," IEEE Conf. on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2017 (Spotlight Presentation).
- H. Jung, Y. Kim, D. Min, C. Oh, and K. Sohn, "Depth prediction from a single image with conditional adversarial networks," IEEE Conf. on Image Processing (ICIP), 2017.
- J. Lee, H. Jung, Y. Kim, and K. Sohn, "Automatic 2D-to-3D conversion using multi-scale deep neural network," IEEE Conf. on Image Processing (**ICIP**), 2017.
- Y. Kim, C. Oh, and K. Sohn, "Edge-aware image smoothing using commute time distance," IEEE Conf. on Image Processing (ICIP), 2016.
- H. Jung, C. Oh, Y. Kim, and K. Sohn, "Depth extraction from a single image based on block-matching and robust regression," Electronic Imaging
- Y. Kim, S. Choi, C. Oh, and K. Sohn, "A majorize-minimize approach for high-quality depth upsampling," IEEE Conf. on Image Processing (ICIP),
- · C. Oh, S. Ryu, Y. Kim, and K. Sohn, "Sparse edit propagation for high resolution image using support vector machines," IEEE Conf. on Image Processing (ICIP), 2015.
- S. Kim, Y. Kim, and K. Sohn, "Structure-aware depth super-resolution using Gaussian mixture model," Electronic Imaging (EI), 2015.
- Y. Kim, S. Choi, and K. Sohn, "Data-driven single image depth estimation using weighted median statistics," IEEE Conf. on Image Processing (ICIP), 2014.
- D. Kim, K. Jung, B. Ham, Y. Kim, and K. Sohn, "Normalized tone-mapping operators for color quality improvement in 3DTV," IEEE Conf. on Industrial Electronics and Applications (ICIEA), 2014.

Technical Report

- Y. Kim, D. Min, B. Ham, and K. Sohn, "Efficient splitting-based method for global image smoothing," CoRR.
- Y. Kim, H. Jung, D. Min, and K. Sohn, "Deeply aggregated alternating minimization for image restoration," CORR.

Projects

Multispectral image fusion for improved object detection

Seoul, S.Korea

Oct. 2017 - PRESENT

PROJECT MEMBER / SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- Funded by LIG Nex1 Co. Ltd.
- Constructing a large-scale multispectral image database for object detection
- Developing deep architectures for multispectral image fusion

High quality 2D-to-multiview contents generation from large-scale RGB+D database

Seoul, S.Korea Oct. 2015 - Aug. 2017

PROJECT INSTRUCTOR

- Funded by Institute of Information and Communication Technology (IITP)
- Developed a large-scale RGB-D database for image processing and computer vision
- Developed convolutional neural network for inferring high-quality depth from a single RGB image

Correspondence matching between images in paired camera

Seoul, S.Korea Mar. 2015 - Nov. 2015

PROJECT MEMBER / SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- Funded by Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd.
- Correspondence matching between 20M mono / 4M RGB (8mm baseline) pair
- Disparity estimation between 5M mono / 1M RGB (7 8cm baseline) pair

Fast image processing for DNG viewer/editor in mobile devices

Seoul, S.Korea

May. 2014 - Nov. 2014

PROJECT MEMBER / SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- Funded by LG Electronics CO. Ltd.
- Developed a fast DNG to RGB conversion algorithm for mobile devices
- Developed a fast image editing algorithm for mobile devices

Development of highly efficient and advanced image processing algorithms for auto-stereoscopic 3D display

Seoul, S.Korea

PROJECT MEMBER

Nov. 2013 - Oct. 2016

- · Funded by Ministry of Science, ICT and Future Planning
- Developed advanced image matching algorithm for real-time 3D display

Development of next generation digital TV broadcasting system

Seoul, S.Korea Mar. 2013 - Dec. 2015

PROJECT MEMBER

- Funded by Information Technology Research Center of Ministry of Knowledge Economy
- Developed core technology for 3D/4K and 8K UHDTV broadcasting generation/editing

JANUARY 10, 2018 YOUNGJUNG KIM · CURRICULUM VITAE

Nov. 2013 - Sep. 2014

PROJECT MEMBER / SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- Funded by Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd.
- Reasoning a high quality range data from 2D image
- Data-driven 2D-to-3D conversion system

Patent _____

INTERNATIONAL

DOMESTIC

2017	Application , Method and device for single image depth estimation: 10-2017-0059112	S.Korea
2016	Registration (completion report), Method and device for depth estimation from single image:	S.Korea
	10-2016-0092078	3.Noreu
2016	Registration (completion report), View extrapolation from single image: 10-2016-0094697	S.Korea
2015	Registration, Method and device for multi-spectral cameras: 10-1562163	S.Korea
2015	Registration, Method and device for video editing: 10-1563822	S.Korea

Award ____

2010	Honors, 2nd—Semester	Yonsei University
2011	Highest Honors, 2nd—Semester	Yonsei University
2012	Honors, 1st—Semester	Yonsei University
2017	Outstanding Student Fellow, BK21 Plus Institute of BEST IT Technology	Yonsei University

Professional Activity

STUDENT MEMBER OF IEEE

STUDENT MEMBER OF SIGNAL PROCESSING SOCIETY

REVIEWER FOR JOURNAL

Neurocomputing

Teaching Assistant

2013 Assistant, Digital Signals Processing

Yonsei University, S.Korea

Programming Languages

VISUAL C/C++, MATLAB, OPENCV, OPENGL, LATEX